<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wangzh</title>
    <link>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wangzh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zn-Hans</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:28:41 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wangzh-hao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker初探——Ubuntu14.04上Docker的安装</title>
      <link>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/blog/2018-11/docker%E5%88%9D%E6%8E%A2ubuntu14.04%E4%B8%8Adocker%E7%9A%84%E5%AE%89%E8%A3%85/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:28:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/blog/2018-11/docker%E5%88%9D%E6%8E%A2ubuntu14.04%E4%B8%8Adocker%E7%9A%84%E5%AE%89%E8%A3%85/</guid>
      <description>一直很好奇Docker到底是一个什么工具，还记得实习的时候，部门经理有个任务就是安装Docker，熟悉Docker基本概念与使用。后来我从后端转前端，这事儿就耽搁了下来。恰逢最近公司有业务场景会接触使用Docker，所以趁着好奇心还在就来探索一下。 了解概念 没了解前，我以为Docker是一个能把几台电脑连起来相互使用运行环境和资源的工具，现在觉得自己真是错得离谱。 某种意义上，可以把Docker看成简</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Start</title>
      <link>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/blog/2018-11/new-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:11:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/blog/2018-11/new-start/</guid>
      <description>启程 在很早之前就想着能够有一个自己畅所欲言的地方，花了一天半的时间总算搭建起来啦。这里将会有我的一些牢骚，一些感想，也会po些照片。Whatever，在这里放飞吧~ 接下来 接下来初步规划： 新增一个resume栏，做一份在线简历 尽量抽时间写一些保质保量的技术blog 有什么想表达的会先写下来然后发布在这，比如看完一本书或一部电影的感想 对于生活的感触也会尽量写在这里，与社交媒体相比更自由。若干年后，再回头</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Test</title>
      <link>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/thinking/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wangzh-hao.github.io/thinking/test/</guid>
      <description>The Hitchhiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy is a comedy science fiction series created by Douglas Adams. Originally a radio comedy broadcast on BBC Radio 4 in 1978, it was later adapted to other formats, and over several years it gradually became an international multi-media phenomenon. Adaptations have included stage shows, a &amp;ldquo;trilogy&amp;rdquo; of five books published between 1979 and 1992, a sixth novel penned by Eoin Colfer in 2009, a 1981 TV series, a 1984 computer game, and three series of three-part comic book adaptations of the first three novels published by DC Comics between 1993 and 1996. There were also two series of towels, produced by Beer-Davies, that are considered by some fans to be an &amp;ldquo;official version&amp;rdquo; of The Hitchhiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy, as they include text from the first novel.
Movie A Hollywood-funded film version, produced and filmed in the UK, was released in April 2005, and radio adaptations of the third, fourth, and fifth novels were broadcast from 2004 to 2005. Adams did many of these adaptations, including the novels, the TV series, the computer game, and the earliest drafts of the Hollywood film’s screenplay, and some of the stage shows introduced new material written by Adams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>